Finding Aid for James and Sybil Irwin family papers, 1815-1987
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Miscellaneous
  - Recipes and Remedies (Box 5)
  - Rice & Champlin Cash Book, Sharon Mills 1856-1867 (Box 5)
  - Scripture Readings 1835 (Box 5)
  - Shopping List (Box 5)
  - "Songs Collected by John E. Irwin and Others" (Box 5)
- Postcards
  - Edinburgh, Scotland Postcards From Irene Hume (Box 6)
  - Charles C. Irwin 1917 (Box 6)
  - Mrs. Donald M. Irwin 1944 (Box 6)
  - Fred C. Irwin 1906-1938 (Box 6)
  - Harriet Irwin 1911-1913 (Box 6)
  - Harriet Irwin Postcard Album 1904-1918 (Box 6)
  - Helen Winifred Irwin 1917 (Box 6)
  - John E. and Amy (Rice) Irwin 1900-1927 (Box 6)
  - Max H. Irwin 1906-1949 (Box 6)
  - Elizabeth Rice 1908-1926 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous Holiday Cards (Box 6)